{"data":[{"question":"A watch and chain ___ on the floor of the room.","a":"was found","b":"were found","c":"have found","d":"has found","answer":"1","explain":"\n- \"A watch and chain\" refers to a thing - singular verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The editor and publisher of the magazine ___ something strange since this morning.","a":"is doing","b":"are doing","c":"has been doing","d":"have been doing","answer":"3","explain":"\n- \"The editor and publisher\" refers to the same person - singular verb ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The fear of robbery and kidnapping _________ many people to flee Lebanon.","a":"has been caused","b":"has caused","c":"have been caused","d":"have caused","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Do not be misled by a phrase that comes between the subject and the verb. The verb agrees with the subject, not with a noun or pronoun in the phrase \n- The subject is \" The fear of\"- singular ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Conditions in Red China ___ so severe that many refugees have risked death to escape.","a":"has grown","b":"is growing","c":"have been grown","d":"have grown","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Do not be misled by a phrase that comes between the subject and the verb. The verb agrees with the subject, not with a noun or pronoun in the phrase \n- The subject is \" conditions\"-plural ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"No one but nurses and doctors ___ the fact that the child will die of cancer.","a":"knows","b":"know","c":"knew","d":"have known","answer":"1","explain":"\n- The core subject of the sentence is \"No one\", and \"but nurses and doctors\" is modifier - singular verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I didn't know lots of money ___ on this experiment.","a":"have been spent","b":"had been spent","c":"has been spent","d":"has spent","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Past perfect: The Past Perfect expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past (I didn't know) \n- Past perfect tense - passive voice: had + been + pp","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"It is better to lose one's life than ___.","a":"if you lose your spirit","b":"losing your spirit","c":"to lose one's spirit","d":"your spirit getting lost","answer":"3","explain":"\n- In the blank should be a verb which has the same form as \"to lose\" ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Mailing a letter a few days early is better than ___.","a":"run the risk of late arrival","b":"running the risk of its arriving late","c":"to run the risk of its arriving late","d":"to run the risk of late arriving","answer":"2","explain":"\n- In the blank should be a verb which has the same form as \"mailing\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The new stores will operate in thirty cities around the country and ___.","a":"five executives running them","b":"run by five executives","c":"five executives to run them","d":"be run by five executives","answer":"4","explain":"\n- In the blank should be a verb which has the same form as \"operate\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Six of the players from the Tigers ___ to participate in the All Star Game.","a":"have been chosen","b":"has been chosen","c":"have chosen","d":"have been choosing","answer":"1","explain":"\n- \"Of phrase \" some of, all of, none of, the rest of...): look at the noun after the preposition to determine whether to use a singular or plural verb. If the object of the preposition is singular, use a singular verb. If the object of the preposition is plural, use a plural verb \n- Players from the Tigers is plural","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}